Curriculum Vitae

YOOBAE KIM

YOOBAE KIM

Emerite Professor of SungKyunKwan University

laguna Woods, CA, USA

yoobae@gmail.com

17348349103

Professional summary

Some combination of the academic background of social science, art, and technology will generate referrals for a new world of

creative job building and educational contents. Experiences of effective instructor and problem-solver with modern technological society will contribute to attain a challenging goal toward developing curricula to integrating humanity, art, and technology.

Skills

Adobe Photoshop	
	70%
Photography	
	80%
Maya	
	20%
Media	
	500/

20%

Languages

English

70%

Korean

100%

Publications

- 벼랑끝에서 날개를 펴라, 서림출판, 2020
- 99 먼째 이력서를 쓰는 젊음에게, 맥하, 2004
- 새로운 도전, 희망찬 미래-생산적 복지, 에디터, 2001
- 김대중, 생산적 복지의 길, 일본 마이니치 신문사, 2002
- 위기가 기회다(공저), 다산출판사,1998
- 노동경제학, 박영사,
- 화폐금융론, 박영사,
- (연구논문))기업의 구조조정과 고용 실업대책 등 다수

Work Experience

• Professor & Official Representative of Global Students, LeTouneau University, Texas

2011 - 2013

Vice-Chairman, WorldSkills International, Netherland

2003 - 2011

• Professor, SungKyunKwan University, Seoul, Korea

1978 - 2008

• President, Human Resource Development, Seoul, Korea

2002 - 2003

Minister, Ministry of Welfare and Patriot, Seoul, Korea

2000 - 2001

• Senior Secretary of Presidency, Presidency Office, Seoul, Korea

1999 - 2000

• Chief Technical Advisor, International Labour Office, Lagos, Nigeria

1990 - 1992

• Senior Research Economist, Korea International Economic Institution, Korea

1977 - 1978

Education

University of Texas at Dallas, USA

2017-2019

Master Degree in Art and Science! All I need to know in one place

MA thesis: "VISUALIZATION OF TRANSFORMING SOCIO_POLITICAL PROCESS--3D Mapping Techniques with MadMapper"

Eastfield College, Mesquite, Texas, USA

2013 - 2015

Certificate of Media Art

University of Illinois at Urbana-Champain, USA

1973 - 1977

Ph. D. & Master Degree in Economics!

Ph. D. Disserttation: Forecasting of the Mapower Requirements in a Rapidly Developing Country - Case Study of Korea

Yonsei University, Seoul, Korea

1963 - 1967

Bachelor Degree in Economics

Find me on social media.

Powered by <u>w3.css</u>